{
    "subject": "Pauline_Koch",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Hermann_Einstein",
    "human_readable": "Pauline Koch is married to Hermann Einstein.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8924286365509033,
            "question": "Who is married to Hermann Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8297088742256165,
            "question": "Is Pauline Koch related to Albert Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8086518049240112,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Pauline Koch and Albert Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122358679771423,
            "question": "What is the name of Hermann Einstein's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6259905099868774,
            "question": "What can we learn about Hermann Einstein through his marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5935118198394775,
            "question": "Who are some individuals connected to Hermann Einstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42185768485069275,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Pauline Koch's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3908444941043854,
            "question": "Can you find any sources that provide more details about Pauline Koch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2657628655433655,
            "question": "Are there any known connections between Pauline Koch and science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06310810893774033,
            "question": "What historical context can help us understand this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pauline Koch is married to Hermann Einstein.",
            "html": "yago_14850_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any known connections between Pauline Koch and science?",
            "html": "yago_14850_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any sources that provide more details about Pauline Koch?",
            "html": "yago_14850_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Pauline Koch's background?",
            "html": "yago_14850_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14850_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Hermann Einstein was married to Pauline Koch, and they had a son named Albert Einstein."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Pauline Koch was indeed married to Hermann Einstein, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}